vogacloset.com 2014-12-14

# Privacy Policy | VogaCloset

**BACKGROUND:**

This Policy applies as between you, the User of this Site and VogaCloset Ltd. the owner and provider of this Site.  This Policy applies to our use of any and all Data collected by us in relation to your use of the Site.

**1\. Definitions and Interpretation**

In this Policy the following terms shall have the following meanings: 

**“Data”**

| 

means collectively all information that you submit to VogaCloset via the Site.  This definition shall, where applicable, incorporate the definitions provided in the Data Protection Act 1998;  
  
---|---  
  
**“Cookie”**

| 

means a small text file placed on your computer by this Site when you visit certain parts of the Site and/or when you use certain features of the Site.  Details of the cookies used by this Site are set out in Clause 12;  
  
**“VogaCloset”**

| 

means VogaCloset Ltd. of 24 Bedford Row, London WC1R 4TQ;  
  
**“UK and EU Cookie Law”**

| 

means the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 as amended by the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) (Amendment) Regulations 2011;  
  
**“User”**

| 

means any third party that accesses the Site and is not employed by VogaCloset and acting in the course of their employment; and  
  
**“Site”**

| 

means the website that you are currently using (www.vogacloset.com) and any sub-domains of this site unless expressly excluded by their own terms and conditions.  
  
**2\. Scope of this Policy**

This Policy applies only to the actions of VogaCloset and Users with respect to this Site.  It does not extend to any websites that can be accessed from this Site including, but not limited to, any links we may provide to social media websites.

**3\. Data Collected**

Without limitation, any of the following Data may be collected by this Site from time to time:

3.1  **[** name; **]**

3.2  **[** date of birth; **]**

3.3  **[** gender; **]**

3.4  **[** job title; **]**

3.5 **  [**profession; **]**

3.6 **  [**contact information such as email addresses and telephone numbers; **]**

3.7  **[** demographic information such as post code, preferences and interests; **]**

3.8  **[** IP address (automatically collected); **]**

3.9  **[** web browser type and version (automatically collected); **]**

3.10  **[** operating system (automatically collected); **]**

3.11  **[** a list of URLs starting with a referring site, your activity on this Site, and the site you exit to (automatically collected); **]**

**4\. Our Use of Data**

4.1  Any personal Data you submit will be retained by VogaCloset for one year.

4.2  Unless we are obliged or permitted by law to do so, and subject to Clause 5, your Data will not be disclosed to third parties.  This includes our affiliates and / or other companies within our group.

4.3  All personal Data is stored securely in accordance with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998.  For more details on security see Clause 11 below.

4.4  Any or all of the above Data may be required by us from time to time in order to provide you with the best possible service and experience when using our Site. 

Specifically, Data may be used by us for the following reasons:

4.4.1  **[** internal record keeping; **]**

4.4.2  **[** improvement of our products / services; **]**

4.4.3  **[** transmission by email of promotional materials that may be of interest to you; **]**

4.4.4  **[** contact for market research purposes which may be done using email, telephone, fax or mail.  Such information may be used to customize or update the Site. **]**

4.5 We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any third parties

**5\. Third Party Websites and Services**

5.1  VogaCloset may, from time to time, employ the services of other parties for dealing with matters that may include, but are not limited to, payment processing, delivery of purchased items, search engine facilities, advertising and marketing.  The providers of such services do not have access to certain personal Data provided by Users of this Site.

5.2  Any Data used by such parties is used only to the extent required by them to perform the services that VogaCloset requests.  Any use for other purposes is strictly prohibited.  Furthermore, any Data that is processed by third parties shall be processed within the terms of this Policy and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

**6\. Links to Other Websites**

This Site may, from time to time, provide links to other websites.  VogaCloset has no control over such websites and is in no way responsible for the content thereof.  This Policy does not extend to your use of such websites.  Users are advised to read the privacy policy or statement of other websites prior to using them.

**7\. Changes of Business Ownership and Control**

7.1  VogaCloset Ltd. may, from time to time, expand or reduce our business and this may involve the sale and / or the transfer of control of all or part of VogaCloset.  Data provided by Users will, where it is relevant to any part of our business so transferred, be transferred along with that part and the new owner or newly controlling party will, under the terms of this Policy, be permitted to use the Data for the purposes for which it was originally supplied to us.

7.2  In the event that any Data submitted by Users is to be transferred in such a manner, you will not be contacted in advance and informed of the changes.

**8\. Your Right to Withhold Information**

8.1  You may access certain areas of the Site without providing any Data at all.  However, to use all features and functions available on the Site you may be required to submit certain Data.

8.2  You may restrict your internet browser’s use of Cookies.  For more information see Clause 12.

**9\. Accessing your own Data**

You have the right to ask for a copy of any of your personal Data held by VogaCloset (where such data is held).

**10\. Security**

Data security is of great importance to VogaCloset and to protect your Data we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure Data collected via this Site.

**11\. Cookies**

11.1  This Site may place and access certain Cookies on your computer.  VogaCloset uses Cookies to improve your experience of using the Site and to improve our range of products **AND / OR** services.  VogaCloset has carefully chosen these Cookies and has taken steps to ensure that your privacy is protected and respected at all times.

11.2  All Cookies used by this Site are used in accordance with current UK and EU Cookie Law.

11.3  Certain features of the Site depend upon Cookies to function. UK and EU Cookie Law deems these Cookies to be “strictly necessary”.  You can choose to enable or disable Cookies in your internet browser.  By default, most Internet browsers accept Cookies but this can be changed.  For further details, please consult the help menu in your Internet browser.

11.4  You can choose to delete Cookies at any time however you may lose any information that enables you to access the Site more quickly and efficiently including, but not limited to, personalization settings.

11.5  It is recommended that you ensure that your internet browser is up-to-date and that you consult the help and guidance provided by the developer of your internet browser if you are unsure about adjusting your privacy settings.

**12\. Changes to this Policy**

VogaCloset reserves the right to change this Policy as we may deem necessary from time to time or as may be required by law. Any changes will be immediately posted on the Site and you are deemed to have accepted the terms of the Policy on your first use of the Site following the alterations.
